A Gift From Mukara
Fight, to realize my ambitions!
Jun! My dad can't fly! I'd attack him from the sky if I were you!
That's right! Blue Cop! You can fly, right?
Of course!
Do not think you can best me just because you can fly!
That's the same device Red Blitz was using!
The Organizer!
I knew the captain had another one...
So that's how he disappeared without a trace back then...
Dad! Stop it!
You haven't seen anything yet!
Huh? Where did he go?
Blue Cop!!
Are you seeing this?!
The battle of Metal Cardbots that goes beyond human logic is unfolding right before my very eyes!
How did it come to this?
I don't know either...
Speranza's teleportation device, the Organizer...
The captain is using its main function as a means of attack!
I said stop, Dad!
If you overuse the Organizer like that, it'll-
SILENCE!!
Red Blitz!
Why would you do that to Red Blitz, Captain?!
Cielo, attack together!
Blastrain! Set Up!
Be careful!
Mr. Blastrain!
Mr. Train!!
Blastrain!!
This is not the time to worry about others!
Blue Cop! Docking Out!
Roger...!
Rush him from all sides!
Get up already, Spark Bit. We need to join him!
Ow ow ow... He knocked me out along with the enemy. Is he really on our side?
It's just this once. Endure it.
Guess I have no choice!
Ahoy, there. You'll have to get through me first!
Ignore him, we can go around.
Let me battle you too!
Battle, huh?! That's one of my favorite words!
Sky Gallop, what are you doing...?!
Master Crest, we're here!
Drop us off over there.
Yes sir!
Peruru!
Sky Gallop!!
Lady Peruru! What brings you to a dangerous place such as this?
Do we really have to fight like this?
It breaks my heart to be enemies with thee, m'lady.
Yet even when divided, our bond shall be etern-
If we're enemies, we're enemies! I hate this kind of ambiguity you're making!
I have no choice, for I have lost my home. Joined to this land...
My fight must continue forevermore!
Annoying pests!
Sir Rex!
Get on!
'Tis against my chivalry to fight two against one...
Yet there is no freedom for us lest I defeat the Star Guardian!
Blue Cop! Superior Docking!
REX! INFERNO!! (FX-bold phoenixFire)
Blue Cop!
Sir Rex?!
He got overloaded!
Teo! Guys! Over-huh?
Overloaded! It means he's in overdrive!
His circuitry is strained because he overused that device!
I've heard of this before.
An Organizer in overdrive once warped the space around it,
and it blew up an entire town!
What?!
Well that's not good!
An overdriven Organizer wasn't part of my plan...
Now, what are you going to do?
Aah, my phone!
This ends-!
NOW!!!
BLUE COP!!!
Peruru...!
My lady?
His eyes...!
You... Weren't you the descendant of Mukara...?
Yes. Mukara is my ancestor.
Right. I remember now.
Mukara is no longer in this world...
Gigantrex!
You're in danger right now!
I'm in danger?
You're gonna explode at this rate!
Agh, it's hot!
Why were you running towards him when you knew it was dangerous?!
It's better to stay away from him.
But... We need to remove that Organizer from him, quickly!
We'll take it from here!!
I'm gonna save my dad for sure!!
He's going for Peruru!
Stop it already, Captain! Please!!
Guys!
Let me lend you a hand!
Us too!
Hold on. Wait for me!
Blue Cop! Cut off the Organizer!!
Hurry!!
We don't have much time until it explodes!
But... What if I fail...?
Think about that some other time!! I'm putting all my faith in ya!
I know you can do this!
Save him, just like you saved me!
I can't hold on much longer!!
Everyone...
Blue Cop!
Hurry up!!
Please... Save my friend. (FX-italic)
Roger that.
Blue Cop!
Galaxies... (FX-bold blueCop)
Punisher!!! (FX-bold blueShine)
Captain!
Dad!!
Wait!
What?!
Look at his eyes!
Peruru!
Mukara...!
Friends of the Speranza. (FX-italic)
By the time you wake up, I will no longer be in this world. (FX-italic)
But, I hope my descendants will still be with you. (FX-italic)
Please heed my advice and get along with not only my descendants, (FX-italic)
but with everyone on this planet. (FX-italic)
Just as you did with me. (FX-italic)
Peruru... What was that just now?
The head of that spear...
is a piece of Machinasium I gave to Mukara as a token of our friendship.
D-Dad!
Captain!
Is that Gigantrex's...
...true character?
Machinasium?
It is a kind of metal from the planet Machina.
It can be used to heal the wounds of Metal Cardbots,
and sometimes, it functions as a storage medium.
So... Mukara just saved you!
No. Not just him.
Descendant of Mukara, you saved me as well.
Thank you.
All thanks to the gift from Mukara. And my name is Peruru!
Peruru...
And you.
Musclehyde, Cielo, Red Blitz... Thank you for your hard work.
All of you, you have my thanks as well.
Peruru, take good care of Gigantrex.
Okay!
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
Metal Cardbot! Change- Uh?
Peruru!
At last, the Metal Breath is in my grasp!
My power, sealed away by Deus Machina, shall rise again!
No... it can't be...!
It is time for me to return... to my true form!